Guide to the Arthur Jack Viseltear papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Arthur Jack Viseltear papers
1953-1990
MS 811
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
28
The papers document Arthur Jack Viseltear's scholarship and professional interests in the field of public health. They include materials related to his teaching and research, documentation of his professional activities, and personal papers which include his diaries from 1974 to 1989. Unpublished writings include research notebooks for his biography of C.-E. A. Winslow and tapes and transcripts of interviews for his study of the contemporary Yale School of Medicine of his time.
Viseltear, Arthur J. (Arthur Jack), 1938-
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Arthur J. Viseltear, 1977, 1985, and 1988, and of Elaine Viseltear, 1990 and 1997.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Original audiovisual materials (in boxes 46 and 47), as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
Biographical / Historical
The papers document Arthur Jack Viseltear's scholarship and professional interests in the field of public health. They include materials related to his teaching and research, documentation of his professional activities, and personal papers which include his diaries from 1974 to 1989. Unpublished writings include research notebooks for his biography of C.-E. A. Winslow and tapes and transcripts of interviews for his study of the contemporary Yale School of Medicine of his time.
After earning his bachelor's degree in history from Tulane University in 1959, he spent the following year there studying the history of public health. He then moved to UCLA, completing his M.P.H. in 1963 and his Ph.D. in 1965 in history with a focus on the history of medicine.
During the academic year, 1962 1963, he was a teaching assistant at UCLA. As a predoctoral fellow from 1963 to 1964, he did research in English archives. He returned to UCLA as an associate in Medical Care, 1964 1965, and then continued as an associate research historian and lecturer in Public Health from 1965 through 1969. He sought financial support for his graduate training and received several prestigious awards, a predoctoral fellowship from the National Institutes of Health (NIH), a Wellcome Trust grant for research during the summer of 1965, and a grant from the American Philosophical Society in 1966. In September 1969, he went to the Yale School of Medicine as assistant professor where he taught courses in the history of medicine and public health and seminars which focused on health policy, contemporary health issues, and the physician in modern society. He was promoted to the rank of associate professor in 1979.
Milton Roemer, Isidore Falk, and George Rosen significantly influenced Viseltear's life and career as colleagues, mentors, and good friends. Roemer shepherded Viseltear's thesis to completion, helped shift Viseltear's interest from history to public health, guided his first teaching efforts at UCLA, and continued to share professional interests. With Falk, who was teaching public health when he arrived, Viseltear shared an interest in the contemporary health insurance movement. Falk supplied Viseltear with information on Winslow when Viseltear was writing an entry for the Dictionary of American Biography in 1977. Viseltear's interest in writing a full length biography may date from that time. George Rosen's appointment at Yale combined public health and medical history as Viseltear's did. When Rosen died unexpectedly, Viseltear took over his course in the history of medicine.
In 1974, Viseltear was one of the inaugural group of six Robert Wood Johnson Health Policy Fellows selected for a year of seminars at the Institute of Medicine in Washington, D.C. and staff assignment to the U.S. Congress. The fellowships were established by the Institute of Medicine with a grant from the Robert Wood Johnson Foundation to provide outstanding mid career health professionals working in academic settings a better understanding of major issues in health policy and a knowledge of how federal health programs are established. The program was intended to create a more constructive relationship between the academic professionals and the government.
Viseltear first worked with Kentucky Republican Representative Tim Lee Carter, the ranking minority member on the subcommittee on public health and the environment. Viseltear contributed to the National Health Education and Promotion Act of 1975. The Comprehensive Health Insurance Plan [CHIP] was added to this proposal. Viseltear also worked on a proposal for a professional standards review organization. For his second congressional assignment, Viseltear worked with LeRoy Goldman, principal staff assistant to the Senate's health subcommittee chairman, Massachusetts Democratic Senator Edward M. Kennedy. Viseltear interested Goldman in his ideas about health education. They were ultimately incorporated in a bill that became the National Health Information and Disease Control Act of 1976 (S. 1466).
Viseltear also served on the governing councils of the American Association for the History of Medicine and the American Public Health Association (APHA). He was chairman of the Medical Care Section and the Intersectional Council of the American Public Health Association and served as chairman of the NIH Health Study Section on the History of Medicine. He served on Yale University committees including search committees for the dean of the medical school, the associate dean for government and community affairs and the librarian of the Medical Library, as well as committees on planning and priorities, the basic sciences, and tenure policy.
In addition, Viseltear served as a member of the Professions Program Panel of the National Endowment for the Humanities, the Robert Wood Johnson Health Policy Fellowship Board, and the editorial boards of the Journal of the History of Medicine and Allied Sciences, Bulletin of the History of Medicine, Medical Care, Journal of Public Health Policy, The Nation's Health, and the Yale Journal of Biology and Medicine. He was named advisor to the Contemporary Medical Care and Health Policy Collection of the Yale University Library in 1975 and in this capacity wrote grant proposals and made solicitations to build the collection. Viseltear's friends and acquaintances are reflected in the collection, which includes the papers of Isidore Falk, George Rosen, Franz Goldmann, and George Silver.
In 1980, Viseltear led a summer seminar entitled "The Physician in Modern Society" sponsored by the National Endowment for the Humanities. In the same year, he began thinking about a project to create an oral history of the Yale Medical School. He delivered the commencement addresses at the Yale School of Medicine in 1981 and at the School of Epidemiology and Public Health in 1988. In 1983, he was elected to the Connecticut Academy of Science and Engineering. He was co recipient of the Francis Gilman Blake Award for Distinguished Teaching in the medical school in 1988.
Viseltear married Elaine Jean Fedors on February 20, 1966. They had two sons, Jason Adam, born September 14, 1970, and Bennet Franklin, born March 4, 1972. He died on January 7, 1990 after a long bout with cancer.
Scope and Contents
The papers document Viseltear's scholarly interest in the history of public health, his dedication to teaching and to his students, his enthusiasm for the planning and development of government health care policy, and his energetic efforts to fulfill his responsibilities to professional organizations and the university. Of particular note are materials relating to public health policy and the teaching of medicine at Yale. The papers also provide evidence of Viseltear's interest in health insurance, osteopathy, and oral history.
Arrangement
Arranged in six series: I. Correspondence, 1958-1989, n.d. II. Professional Activities, 1963-1989. III. Writings, Speeches and Other Statements, 1959-1989. IV. Teaching Files, 1965-1989, n.d. V. Subject Files, 1969-1986, n.d. VI. Personal Papers and Photographs, 1953-1990, n.d.
Epidemiology -- Study and teaching; Health insurance; Medical care; Medical policy; Medicine -- History; Osteopathic medicine; Public health -- Study and teaching; Contemporary Medical Care and Health Policy Collection; Rosen, George, 1910-1977; Viseltear, Arthur J. (Arthur Jack), 1938-; United States. Congress. Senate. Committee on Health and Public Welfare; American Association for the History of Medicine; American Public Health Association; Yale University -- Faculty; Yale University. School of Medicine
- Correspondence, 1958 1989, undated; Series I
  Scope and Contents
  The series contains correspondence largely concerning Viseltear's professional interests and dating from his graduate school days and forward. The correspondence is predominantly with colleagues about professional matters, and there is only a small amount of correspondence with his family and friends. Additional correspondence is scattered through the remaining five series.
  Viseltear arranged the correspondence in this series in two sections. There are alphabetical files arranged under the name of the correspondent, as well as a section arranged in chronological order. The alphabetical files contain incoming letters and often a carbon of Viseltear's response while the chronological files contain outgoing carbon copies. They also include memoranda and proposals drafted by Viseltear.
  The chronological section can be used to trace the development of issues and projects from conception to fruition or termination. The increase in volume of chronological files in the late 1970s and 1980s reflects Viseltear's burgeoning activities on professional committees. Although there is clearly overlap between the sections and with the correspondence filed in other series, the chronological files provide the most complete record of Viseltear's endeavors.
  The researcher should note that Series II contains letters associated with committee responsibilities and academic issues, Series III contains correspondence relevant to grant proposals and publications, Series IV includes communications with students and administrators, Series V contains subject relevant correspondence, and Series VI has letters concerning career decisions, such as appointments and recruitments.
  - Alphabetical
    - A, 1965-1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Abrams, Herbert, 1968-1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Abrams, Sarah E., 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Adams, Elizabeth C., 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Agran, Larry, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Akpulonu, Lawson, 1969, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Alfin-Slater, Roslyn, 1965-1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Atkins, Elisha, 1977-1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Atwater, Edward, 1982-1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Axelrod, Solomon Jacob, 1966-1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - B, 1965-1989 (Box 1, Folder 11-14)
    - Banta, David, 1975-1982 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Bellis, Elizabeth C., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Benison, Saul, 1969, 1977-1989 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Bennett, Ivan, 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Benz, Edward, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Berliner, Robert, 1974-1983 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Bishop, David, 1968-1973 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Bloch, Jenny, 1965-1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Bolen, James and Jean, 1966-1972 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Boudreau, Joseph, 1963-1988 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Brand, Jeanne, 1979-1989 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Breslow, Devra and Lester, 1968-1989 (Box 1, Folder 26-27)
    - Brieger, Gert H., 1977-1989 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Brown, Theodore M., 1977-1986 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Burchell, Howard B., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Burk, Bernard, 1965-1989 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Bynum, William F., 1977-1987 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - C, 1961-1989 (Box 2, Folder 33-34)
    - Carter, Tim Lee, 1976-1987 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Casey, Edward S., 1979-1983 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Cassedy, James H., 1965-1989 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Chang, Grace, 1978-1987 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Churchill, Frederick B., 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Coggins, Christa, 1983-1986 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Cohart, Edward, 1970-1978 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Cook, Francesca, 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Corey, Seth, 1977-1984 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Culleton, Barbara, 1975-1988 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - D, 1965-1989 (Box 2, Folder 45-46)
    - De Peyster, Frances Lee, 1975-1980 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Donaldson, Robert M., 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Duffy, John, 1967-1989 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Duffy, Thomas P., 1982-1989 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Dwork, Deborah, 1977-1989 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - E, 1964-1989 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Ebbert, Arthur, 1974-1989 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Engel, Jonathan William, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - F, 1963-1989 (Box 3, Folder 55-57)
    - Fabro, J. Alfred, 1977-1985 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Falk, Isidore S., 1969-1984 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Falk, Leslie, 1969-1986 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Fee, Elizabeth, 1980-1989 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Feinstein, Alvan, 1974-1989 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Forbes, Thomas R., 1977-1987 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Freed, James R., 1971-1987 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Fulton, Lucia, 1978-1989 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - G, 1963-1989 (Box 3, Folder 66-68)
    - Gemmill, Daphne deJersey, 1972-1989 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Giamatti, A. Bartlett, 1978-1985 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Gifford, Robert H., 1983-1989 (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Glenn, William W. L., 1971-1989 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Greenberg, Samuel Elliot, 1960-1989 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - H, 1965-1990 (Box 4, Folder 74-76)
    - Hall, A. Rupert, 1962-1965 (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Holmes, Frederick L., 1978-1989 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Hopkins, Carl E., 1965-1987 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - Horstmann, Dorothy M., 1970-1989 (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - Hubbard, John R., 1959-1972 (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - Hudson, Robert P., 1978-1989 (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - Hundert, Edward, 1977-1989 (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - I, 1965-1987 (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - J, 1969-1989 (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - Joy, Robert J. T., 1978-1989 (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - K, 1967-1989 (Box 4, Folder 87-88)
    - Kisch, Arnold I., 1965-1974 (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - L, 1964-1989 (Box 5, Folder 90-91)
    - Langmuir, Alexander D., 1980-1986 (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - M, 1964-1989 (Box 5, Folder 93-95)
    - MacLeod, Roy M., 1964-1989 (Box 5, Folder 96)
    - McCollum, Robert W., 1969-1985 (Box 5, Folder 97)
    - McGinnis, J. Michael, 1977-1989 (Box 5, Folder 98)
    - McIlwain, James T., 1964-1970 (Box 5, Folder 99)
    - MD Publications, Inc., 1969-1984 (Box 5, Folder 100)
    - More, Ellen S., 1985-1989 (Box 5, Folder 101)
    - Myers, Beverlee A., 1968-1987 (Box 5, Folder 102)
    - N, 1964-1989 (Box 6, Folder 103)
    - Nuland, Sherwin B., 1977-1989 (Box 6, Folder 104)
    - Numbers, Ronald L., 1977-1982 (Box 6, Folder 105)
    - O, 1968-1989 (Box 6, Folder 106)
    - O'Malley, Charles Donald, 1960-1974 (Box 6, Folder 107)
    - Oren, Daniel A., 1982-1986 (Box 6, Folder 108)
    - P, 1958-1989 (Box 6, Folder 109-110)
    - Q, 1974-1988 (Box 6, Folder 111)
    - R, 1963-1989 (Box 6, Folder 112-113)
    - Rawson, Richard A., 1965-1989 (Box 6, Folder 114)
    - Raz, Samuel, 1970-1976 (Box 6, Folder 115)
    - Reeder, Leo and Sharon, 1966-1978 (Box 6, Folder 116)
    - Rich, Shirley W., 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 117)
    - Risse, Guenter B., 1976-1989 (Box 6, Folder 118)
    - Roach, Charles W., 1973-1989 (Box 6, Folder 119)
    - Rockefeller Archive Center, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 120)
    - Roemer, Milton and Ruth, 1963-1989 (Box 7, Folder 121-122)
    - Rosen, Beate, 1979-1988 (Box 7, Folder 123)
    - Rosen, George, 1968-1988 (Box 7, Folder 124)
    - Rosenberg, Charles E., 1976-1987 (Box 7, Folder 125)
    - Rosenberg, Leon E., 1980-1989 (Box 7, Folder 126)
    - Rosenkranz, Barbara G., 1973-1989 (Box 7, Folder 127)
    - Rosner, David, 1971-1989 (Box 7, Folder 128)
    - S, 1960-1989 (Box 7, Folder 129-132)
    - Savitt, Todd L., 1981-1989 (Box 7, Folder 133)
    - Schmitt, Hans A., 1961-1970 (Box 7, Folder 134)
    - Segal, Elliot A., 1969 (Box 7, Folder 135)
    - Seggel, Richard L., 1974-1987 (Box 7, Folder 136)
    - Seldin-Somer, Howard, 1983-1989 (Box 8, Folder 137)
    - Sheps, Cecil G., 1973-1989 (Box 8, Folder 138)
    - Sidel, Victor W., 1983-1988 (Box 8, Folder 139)
    - Silver, George A., 1970-1989 (Box 8, Folder 140-141)
    - Snowe, Robert J., 1974-1982 (Box 8, Folder 142)
    - Somers, Anne R., 1975-1989 (Box 8, Folder 143)
    - Spiro, Howard M., 1981-1989 (Box 8, Folder 144)
    - Stevens, Rosemary, 1964-1986 (Box 8, Folder 145)
    - Stevenson, Lloyd G., 1977-1980 (Box 8, Folder 146)
    - Stokes, Joseph, 1967-1969 (Box 8, Folder 147)
    - T, 1965-1989 (Box 8, Folder 148)
    - Temple Beth Tikvah, 1982-1989 (Box 8, Folder 149)
    - Terris, Milton, 1972-1989 (Box 8, Folder 150)
    - Thompson, John D., 1970-1987 (Box 8, Folder 151)
    - Thomson, Elizabeth, 1972-1984 (Box 8, Folder 152)
    - Tiegel, Elliot L., 1966-1986 (Box 8, Folder 153)
    - U, 1964-1987 (Box 8, Folder 154)
    - V, 1966-1987 (Box 8, Folder 155)
    - Viseltear, Elaine, 1965-1971, undated (Box 8, Folder 156)
    - Viseltear, Jason and Bennett, 1978-1989 (Box 9, Folder 157)
    - Viseltear family, 1960-1989 (Box 9, Folder 158)
    - von Staden, Heinrich, 1977-1984 (Box 9, Folder 159)
    - W, 1964-1989 (Box 9, Folder 160-161)
    - Warner, John Harley, 1988-1989, undated (Box 9, Folder 162)
    - Y, Z, 1968-1988 (Box 9, Folder 163)
    - Young, James Harvey, 1980-1989 (Box 9, Folder 164)
    - Unidentified, 1963-1989, undated (Box 9, Folder 165)
  - Chronological
    - 1969 July-1970 December (Box 9, Folder 166-167)
    - 1971 January-1975 March (Box 10, Folder 168-178)
    - 1975 April-1979 May (Box 11, Folder 179-188)
    - 1979 June-1983 (Box 12, Folder 189-200)
    - 1984-1987 January (Box 13, Folder 201-213)
    - 1987 February-1989 December (Box 14, Folder 214-226)
- Professional Activities, 1963-1989; Series II
  Arranged alphabetically, this series documents Viseltear's work on committees of the American Public Health Association and the American Association for the History of Medicine, his year as a Robert Wood Johnson Health Policy Fellow and his contributions to various Yale University committees. The files of his Robert Wood Johnson Healthy Policy Fellowship are particularly rich in details of the day by day development of health policy legislation and of Viseltear's influence. They include successive drafts of legislation, briefings on bills, drafts of floor statements to introduce bills, the selection of witnesses to present testimony before Congress, prompt cards, questions to ask witnesses, as well as reviews of their testimony.
  There are voluminous files on Viseltear's work as chairman of the Medical Care Section of the APHA, of the Yale Medical School Council, and of the Weinerman Memorial Fund Committee. The series contains his grant proposals for funding his own research as well as for the establishment of the Contemporary Medical Care and Health Policy Collection (CMCHPC). The files for the Yale University Library document his efforts to develop and encourage contributions to the CMCHPC. Materials gathered under the general headings for Yale University and the Yale School of Medicine document Viseltear's participation on committees on which he did not play a major role.
  The series also includes files related to Viseltear's editorial work on several professional journals, including the Journal of the History of Medicine and Allied Sciences, the Journal of Biology and Medicine, and the Bulletin of the History of Medicine. His participation in the 1987 Bellagio Conference on Education in Public Health is documented, as well as the subsequent efforts to publish a book on the proceedings. The Exhibits files delineate Viseltear's contributions to three exhibits in the Cushing Rotunda of the Yale Cushing/Whitney Medical Library. Papers associated with Viseltear's activities for the Nathan Smith and Beaumont Clubs have been added to the archives of the two societies at the Medical Historical Library of the Yale Cushing/Whitney Medical Library.
  - American Association for the History of Medicine
    - General, 1965-1989 (Box 15, Folder 1-14)
    - Bulletin of the History of Medicine, 1965-1989 (Box 16, Folder 15-16)
  - American Association of Legal History, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - American Journal of Public Health [memorial program in tribute to George Rosen], 1977 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - American Osler Society, 1978-1989 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - American Public Health Association (Box 16)
  - General, 1969-1989 (Box 16, Folder 20-28)
  - Intersectional Council, 1979-1981 (Box 16, Folder 29-31)
  - Intersectional Council, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Medical Care Section
    - General, 1979-1982 (Box 17, Folder 33-35)
    - Annual reports, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - "Honoring George A. Silver" [program], 1980 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Medical Care [journal], 1980-1981 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Nominating Committee, 1979-1981 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Pharmacy Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Program Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Social Policy Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Arno Press Project: Public Health in America, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Association of American Medical Colleges, 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Bellagio Conference on Education in Public Health in the United States and the United Kingdom (Box 17)
  - General, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - "A History of Public Health Education: Britain and the United States Contrasted" [book proposed], 1987-1989 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    General note
    See also: Series III, folder 39
  - Committee on Corporate Responsibility. Advisory Council on Education for Health, 1978-1980 (Box 18, Folder 47-48)
  - Commonwealth Fund: "The Evolution of the Medical School Deanship" [proposal], 1976 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Connecticut Academy of Science and Engineering, 1978-1989 (Box 18, Folder 50-51)
  - Connecticut Public Health Association, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Exhibits
    - "Medical History at Yale" with Thomas P. Gariepy, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - "Medicine and Literature" with Enid Peschel, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - "Charles-Edward Amory Winslow, 1877-1957", 1987 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Expert Panel on Health Education, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Falk, I. S. [memorial service], 1984 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Good Health in America [conference], 1977 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Hannah Institute for History of Medicine, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - Health and Welfare Planning Association, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - Institute of Medicine [proposal], 1985 (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - Johns Hopkins University Press, 1980-1985 (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - Journal of History of Medicine and Allied Sciences, 1965-1989 (Box 18, Folder 63-65)
  - Macy Foundation-Yale University Conference on History and Health Policy [proposal], 1971 (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - Milbank Memorial Fund, 1968-1987 (Box 19, Folder 67-68)
  - National Association for Public Health Policy, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 69)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities
    - "The Physician in Society" [proposal], 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 70)
      See also: Series IV, folder 123
    - Professions Program panels, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 71)
  - National Institutes of Health